Josh Dixon

I have over nine years professional experience in digital content creation, sales and marketing, specialising in photography and graphic design. Looking for the right opportunity to grow and develop in the technology industry - leveraging my skills in a UX/UI designer role.

Programming Experience

Development Portfolio Website

My portfolio website demonstrates my ability to apply my knowledge of wireframing accessible design into a fully functioning responsive site. Built utilising HTML, CSS, JavaScript and the Bootstrap framework.

The Masters Golf Tournament Website

This web page was built using the Materialize UI component library and hosted with Netlify. The page is responsive and was built with user accessibility in mind.

Education

Worksop College

Sept 2011 - Jun 2013

A levels in Design & Technology, Applied Business and Physical Education

Grove School

Sept 2006 - Jun 2011

5 GCSE's A-C including English and Mathematics

Work Experience

Freelance Sports Photography

Jan 2012 - Present

- Shoot, edit and caption imagery of sports events, game action, products, press conferences, and media days
- Maintain and organise the image archive for professinal football clubs.
- Produce all content in line with the clients digital strategy and style.
- Proven ability to work in high pressure and fast paced environments.

Ice Locker - Retail Assistant

Feb 2016 - Aug 2020

- Process online orders and handle incoming deliveries.
- Train staff in maintain high standards of customer service and customer care.
- · Correctly advise and fit ice sports equipment.
- Liase with suppliers and produce purchase orders for four stores.
- Day-to-day stock management and store duties.
- Manage social media accounts, produce engaging content and oversee paid advertising.

I'm a Nottingham based web developer and I create modern, responsive and user-friendly web experiences. I'm a creative individual with a passion for all things design.

Contact

joshdixon1995@hotmail.co.uk

07753334432

Dev Portfolio

Design Portfolio

Photography Portfolio

LinkedIn

GitHub

Technical Skills

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

Unit Testing

Node.js

Bootstrap

Materialize

Version control

Responsive Design

Wireframing

Photoshop / Illustrator

Certifications

UX and Accessible Design

UAL Creative Computing Institute

AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials

Amazon Web Services Training